<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The cloud architect's playbook</title><link>https://matthiasgoetze.com/de/</link><description>Recent content on The cloud architect's playbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-de</language><copyright>Test</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 15:30:25 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matthiasgoetze.com/de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Experimente mit Chat GPT</title><link>https://matthiasgoetze.com/de/posts/general/chatgpt/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 15:30:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matthiasgoetze.com/de/posts/general/chatgpt/</guid><description>Chat GPT ist aktuell in aller Munde, natürlich habe ich auch ein paar Experimente damit durchgeführt. Diesmal habe ich versucht ein Mathe-Rätsel von der AI lösen zu lassen, hier was dabei raus kam:
Anmerkung: Ich habe die Höflichkeits-Sätze der AI weg gelassen um den Text leserlicher zu halten.
Meine Anfrage ChatGPTs Antwort Kommentar Imagine a 4 digit number that multiplied by 4 gives you the same number written backwards One possible solution is the number 2002.</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://matthiasgoetze.com/de/posts/general/helloworld/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 15:30:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matthiasgoetze.com/de/posts/general/helloworld/</guid><description>Aller Anfang ist schwer &amp;hellip; Da bin ich also mit meinem eigenen Blogprojekt. Entstanden daraus, dass ich bei YouTube ein Video über HUGO Statische Websites gesehen habe und es eine spannende Herausforderung fand.
Das Video ist jetzt schon wieder mehrere Monate her, aber wer hat schon Zeit sich dann um die Projekte zu kümmern. Letztendlich waren es die Weihnachtsfeiertage 2022 die mir die nötige Zeit geschenkt haben mich jetzt doch noch um den Blog zu kümmern.</description></item><item><title>Markdown Cheatsheet</title><link>https://matthiasgoetze.com/de/posts/markdown/cheatsheet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 14:50:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matthiasgoetze.com/de/posts/markdown/cheatsheet/</guid><description>To be honest, this list is stolen, stolen from the original author of the TOHA theme I&amp;rsquo;m using for this site. Thank you for preparing this is, so I can use it as well @hossainemruz
This is a sample post intended to test the followings:
A different post author. Table of contents. Markdown content rendering. Math rendering. Emoji rendering. Markdown Syntax Rendering Headings The following HTML &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;—&amp;lt;h6&amp;gt; elements represent six levels of section headings.</description></item><item><title>Search Results</title><link>https://matthiasgoetze.com/de/search/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://matthiasgoetze.com/de/search/</guid><description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml ``` [outputs] home = [&amp;ldquo;HTML&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;JSON&amp;rdquo;] ```</description></item><item><title>Search Results</title><link>https://matthiasgoetze.com/de/search/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://matthiasgoetze.com/de/search/</guid><description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml ``` [outputs] home = [&amp;ldquo;HTML&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;JSON&amp;rdquo;] ```</description></item><item><title>Checklist</title><link>https://matthiasgoetze.com/de/notes/blog/todo/checklist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://matthiasgoetze.com/de/notes/blog/todo/checklist/</guid><description> Checkliste Übersetzungen Sections ins englische Übersetzen Intro-Seite About Seite Skills Erfahrung Projekte Checkliste Übersetzungen Blogposts schreiben (DE&amp;amp;EN) Hello World Post Erster Post (Beruflich)</description></item></channel></rss>